var questions = [
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for potatoes?',
    answers: ['pateta', 'tamato', 'aniani', 'karoti'],
    correctAnswer: 'pateta'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for tomatoes?',
    answers: ['pateta', 'tamato', 'aniani', 'karoti'],
    correctAnswer: 'tamato'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for onions?',
    answers: ['pateta', 'tamato', 'aniani', 'karoti'],
    correctAnswer: 'aniani'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for carrots?',
    answers: ['pateta', 'tamato', 'aniani', 'karoti'],
    correctAnswer: 'karoti'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for apples?',
    answers: ['apu', 'tamato', 'aniani', 'karoti'],
    correctAnswer: 'apu'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for bananas?',
    answers: ['apu', 'fa\'l', 'aniani', 'karoti'],
    correctAnswer: 'fa\'l'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for oranges?',
    answers: ['apu', 'fa\'l', 'moli', 'karoti'],
    correctAnswer: 'moli'

  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for bread?',
    answers: ['apu', 'fa\'l', 'moli', 'falaoa'],
    correctAnswer: 'falaoa'

  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for milk?',
    answers: ['susu', 'fa\'l', 'moli', 'falaoa'],
    correctAnswer: 'susu'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Samoan word for butter?',
    answers: ['susu', 'pata', 'moli', 'falaoa'],
    correctAnswer: 'pata'
  },
  {
    question: 'Hello',
    answers: ['Fa\'afetai','Tālofa', 'Tūlou', 'Leai'],
    correctAnswer: 'Tālofa'
  },
  {
    question: 'Good bye',
    answers: ['Fa\'afetai','Tālofa', 'Tālofa', 'Fā soifua'],
    correctAnswer: 'Fā soifua'
  },
  {
    question: 'Yes',
    answers: ['\'Ioe','Tālofa', 'Malō', 'Leai'],
    correctAnswer: '\'Ioe'
  },
  {
    question: 'No',
    answers: ['\'Ioe','Leai', 'Tūlou', 'Malō'],
    correctAnswer: '\'Ioe'
  },
  {
    question: 'How are you?',
    answers: ['\'O ā mai \'oe','Fa\'afetai fo\'i.', 'Tōfā soifua.', 'Manuia le taeao'],
    correctAnswer: '\'O ā mai \'oe'
  },
  {
    question: 'Fine, thank you',
    answers: ['\'O ā mai \'oe.','Manuia, fa\'afetai.', 'Fa\'amolemole', 'Fa\'amālūlū atu'],
    correctAnswer: 'Manuia, fa\'afetai.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is your name?',
    answers: ['\'O ā mai \'oe.','\'O ai lou suafa?', 'Tōfā soifua', 'Fa\'amālūlū atu'],
    correctAnswer: '\'O ai lou suafa?'
  },
  {
    question: 'I\'m sorry',
    answers: ['Fa\'amālūlū atu','Fa\'afetai fo\'i.', 'O ā mai \'oe', 'Manuia le taeao'],
    correctAnswer: 'Fa\'amālūlū atu'
  },
  {
    question: 'Thank you',
    answers: ['\'O ā mai \'oe.','Fa\'afetai.', 'Tōfā soifua', 'Fa\'amālūlū atu'],
    correctAnswer: 'Fa\'afetai.'
  },
  {
    question: 'I don\'t know',
    answers: ['\'O ā mai \'oe.','Ou te leiloa', 'Manuia le po', 'Ia manuia'],
    correctAnswer: 'Ou te leiloa'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where is the toilet?',
    answers: ['\'O ā mai \'oe.','Fa\'afetai.', '\'Ou te lē mālamalama.', 'O fea le faleuila?'],
    correctAnswer: 'O fea le faleuila?'
  },
  {
    question: 'Call the police!',
    answers: ['Fia ola!','Vili le leoleo!', '\'Ou te lē mālamalama.', 'Tulou lava'],
    correctAnswer: 'Vili le leoleo!'
  }
];

module.exports = questions;
